https://msmugs.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Privacy Policy
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.
For the best experience on our site, be sure to turn on Javascript in your browser.
Menu
ShopGifts by OccasionUpcomingFather's DayMother's DayPopularBirthdayRetirementNew BabyCongratulationsWeddingEngagementMore OccasionsValentine'sEasterFather's DayChristmasExam ResultsEnd Of TermThank YouGraduationGifts by RecipientFamily & FriendsMumDadSistersBrothersChildrenGrandparentsFriendsFamiliesInterestsCat LoversDog LoversGifts by CategoryAnimals & NatureBirdsCatsDogsFlowersGeneralTreesOceansAutumnEducational & InformativeArtGeographyHistoryLanguagesLiteratureSciencesMathsMusicFood & DrinkGinCoffeeTeaProseccoWineChocolateCakeVegan/VegetarianHumourQuotesAnimalsPostersPlacesLondonScottishSport & FitnessCricketCyclingFootballFishingGeneralGolfRugbyRunningPersonalised GiftsGeneralBirthdaysWeddingsCongratulationsThank YouNew BabyDesignersAlice ScottAlways SparkleAnnie CampbellBabs PeaseBespoke VerseBetsy BennBluebellgrayBrainwavesBrave Scottish GiftsBroraCammy ThomsonChris McCollCOCO ChocolatierCoulson MacleodEdward LearEdward MonktonElspeth GardnerEpicGeniusGingerBeeHeidi NicoleHey! Holla Hole In My PocketHolly LasseterKate SpurwayKatie AbeyKatrin MoyeKim HaskinsKiwi Print StudioLisa MacarioLola & GilbertLotta JansdotterLouise TateLoveIglooLucy LoveheartMadeleine FloydManifestoMary FellowsMclagganMegan ClaireNatty MaidOrla KielyPicturemapsQuentin BlakeRaw XclusiveRob RyanRoderick FieldRosie Made A ThingSally ScaffardiSimon DrewSnap To GridStop The ClockSue FenlonSummersdaleTeresa GreenThornback & PeelCinnamon AitchTyrell KatzTravel MugsBaublesGift BoxesNew ArrivalsFAQBlogBespokeSize Guide
SIZE
HEIGHT
DIAMETER
CAPACITY
Small
75mm
65mm
200ml
300ml
*Please note: all sizes are approximate and for illustrative purposes..
†Large china has been discontinued. Dimensions provided for reference only.
Account
Settings
Language
Default Store View
Trade Customers
Currency
GBP - British Pound
EUR - Euro
USD - US Dollar
Rated "Excellent" by our customers
Free UK delivery over £40
Personalised Gifts
Made in the UK
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Mclaggan uses and protects any information
that you give Mclaggan when you use this website.
Mclaggan is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website,
then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Mclaggan may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.
You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
If you have opted in to receive direct marketing, we may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we
think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure,
we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure
the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic
and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical
analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful
and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. Once you leave our website, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst
visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
if you have created an account on our website, you can delete your data using the Privacy Tools once logged in.
If you have created an account on our website, you can manage your newsletter preferences using the Newsletter Subscription page. Customers will not receive direct marketing by default (i.e. you must "opt in").
If you subscribed to our newsletter without creating an account, you can unsubscribe by following the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of emails, or by emailing us at marketing@msmugs.com.
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes,
you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at marketing@msmugs.com.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to
.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete,
please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address.
We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE name
COOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Privacy and Cookie PolicySearch TermsOrders and ReturnsAdvanced SearchContact UsSite Map
